// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "I ....... 15 years old.",
  answer: "am",
  options: [
    "were",
    "don't",
    "am",
    "went"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Do you eat insects?",
  answer: "No, i don't",
  options: [
    "yes",
    "no",
    "Yes, i do",
    "No, i don't"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "How ....... water did she have?",
  answer: "much",
  options: [
    "many",
    "long",
    "much",
    "often"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "He ....... a junior chess competition when he was 10 years old.",
  answer: "won",
  options: [
    "wins",
    "won",
    "win",
    "to win"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "He took a car by ....... .",
  answer: "himself",
  options: [
    "himself",
    "myself",
    "themselves",
    "ourselves"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "I ....... going to wash my hair tomorrow.",
  answer: "am",
  options: [
    "will",
    "are",
    "am",
    "do"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "I buy things ....... myself.",
  answer: "by",
  options: [
    "as",
    "by",
    "at",
    "with"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "I’m going to the ....... as I have a toothache.",
  answer: "dentist",
  options: [
    "farmer",
    "dentist",
    "grocer",
    "baker"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "The camera is ......., it costs a lot of money.",
  answer: "expensive",
  options: [
    "expensive",
    "high",
    "cheap",
    "good"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "What ....... you do yesterday?",
  answer: "did",
  options: [
    "have",
    "did",
    "will",
    "are"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "It ....... delicious.",
  answer: "looks",
  options: [
    "to look",
    "looking",
    "look",
    "looks"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "This is my house. I’m the ....... of it.",
  answer: "owner",
  options: [
    "king",
    "friend",
    "owner",
    "chef"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "I like ....... soup.",
  answer: "chicken",
  options: [
    "chicken",
    "lemonade",
    "apple",
    "fish"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "Where did the first chips factory ....... ?",
  answer: "open",
  options: [
    "opens",
    "opening",
    "opened",
    "open"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "Did she ....... the fish?",
  answer: "eat",
  options: [
    "eat",
    "taken",
    "eaten",
    "eat to"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "He ....... Swimming in the pool.",
  answer: "likes",
  options: [
    "like",
    "does",
    "likes",
    "will"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "Which bus ....... i get?",
  answer: "should",
  options: [
    "were",
    "should",
    "have",
    "when"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "....... was your meal?",
  answer: "How",
  options: [
    "How",
    "When",
    "Where",
    "What"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "....... you play everyday?",
  answer: "Do",
  options: [
    "Did",
    "Will",
    "When",
    "Do"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "When ....... they go to the school?",
  answer: "did",
  options: [
    "have",
    "did",
    "do",
    "were"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: "When will ....... cook the food?",
  answer: "she",
  options: [
    "she",
    "her",
    "herself",
    "himself"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 22,
  question: "I ....... a lot of homeworks yesterday.",
  answer: "had",
  options: [
    "have",
    "had",
    "am",
    "was"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];